so now that we have seen how function
inlining works let's do function
inlining quiz so let's say we have a
load
into a0 which would be the first
argument of a function and then we call
a function and then we store the result
of the function somewhere else let's say
that what the function is doing is it's
computing the square of this value and
then adding the second parameter to it
and that's what it returns so it's
simply returning the you know square of
the first parameter plus the second
parameter let's say we have a processor
where load takes two cycles to do call
takes two cycles to do red takes two
cycles to do and store word and add are
one cycle per instruction and the
multiply instruction takes three cycles
before we can use the result the
question for you is after scheduling
this and this together will take how
many cycles so how many cycles from the
point we start the load until we are
done with the store and after inlining
and then scheduling how many cycles does
this take